A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Ann C. Whitman, Gubernatorial, Series 35 FA374
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Campaign 1968, 4; 3 Document Box(es)
  - Vermont, June 28, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 314)
    Burlington
  - Virginia, June 28, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 315)
    Williamsburg
  - Washington, July 2, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 316)
    Seattle
  - Washington, District of Columbia, June 21, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 317)
  - West Virginia, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 318)
  - Wisconsin, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 319)
  - Wyoming, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 320)